<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GadiCustomer</string>
    <string name="tagline">Experience beauty in every detail with our car app ! Where style meets Convenience!</string>
    <string name="boardingtagline">Exceptional service, extraordinary vehicles , Where professionalism meets unparalleled expertise</string>
    <string name="login">Login your account using Email, password or else create account</string>
    <string name="register">Looks like you doesnot have account . Please Create your account</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="GadiPolicy">GaadiBazaar collects technical information such as IP addresses, login details, operating systems, browser types, and search histories. This data is used for user onboarding and is retained as long as the user remains a customer, in compliance with applicable laws. They also collect location data during the onboarding and KYC verification processes. Additional information, like bank statements and vehicle images, may be required for loan processing and legal compliance. The collected data is used to enable platform services, process loans, assess loan amounts and interest rates, and ensure legal compliance</string>
    <string name="GadiSupport">Gadi Support gathers information provided during user registration, such as name, age, email address, location, and phone number. They also collect transaction-related information, GPS data, and technical details about devices used to access their services. This information is utilized to provide and improve their services, conduct research, personalize user experience, and ensure security. They emphasize adherence to ethical standards in gathering, using, and safeguarding user information.</string>
    <string name="DataPolicy">Ed-Gaadi collects user-provided information during registration, such as name, age, email address, location, and phone number. They also gather transaction-related information, GPS data, and technical details about devices used to access their services. This information is used to analyze trends, conduct research, personalize user experience, and improve their services. They emphasize safeguarding the confidentiality of user information through physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards</string>

</resources>